# Franco Miranda

# Full Stack Developer

■ franco.miranda.dev@gmail.com 
 ■ Buenos Aires, Argentina 
 ■ Website in LinkedIn

# **Profile**

I am a passionate Full Stack Developer with over 1 year of experience in web development and a solid background in Computer Engineering. I enjoy working on challenging projects that allow me to learn and grow. My commitment to excellence and continuous improvement drives me to seek effective and efficient technical solutions.

# **Professional Experience**

#### Developer Full Stack

2023 – present

Freelance

- Payment Gateway Integration: Worked closely with national payment service providers and international to integrate payment gateways into your website. As a result of this implementation, we experienced a notable 20% increase in the number of successful transactions. Tech stack: JavaScript, Node.js, Express.js, MySQL, Stripe.
- Design and Development of an Authentication System: I developed a secure authentication system that requires
  users to generate and use tokens to access their accounts. This solution significantly improves the security of
  authentication on the website. Technologies used: JavaScript, Node.js, Express.js, React.js, MySQL, JWT.

Developer Full Stack Jr

2022 - 2023

Mate - Consultora de Software

- Development and maintenance of web applications using technologies such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React.js, Node.js, Express and MongoDB.
- Design and development of efficient and scalable database structures for web applications and systems, including the implementation of **SOL** queries.
- Design of attractive and responsive user interfaces, optimizing the user experience and improving the usability of the final products
- Troubleshooting and debugging

# **Education**

#### **Computer Engineering**

2020 – present

Universidad Nacional de La Matanza

# **Certificates**

- Universidad Java De Cero a Experto
- The Complete 2023 Web Development Bootcamp ℰ
- Universidad Desarrollo Web FrontEnd Web Developer! ⊗

# **Projects**

#### To Do List ∂

Node.js, Express, MongoDB, Bootstrap

- Web application with user registration that allows you to keep track of the to do list
- User authentication and registration
- Use of non-relational database to store user information and task list

### Shop Shoes ∂

React.is, Chakra UI, Express.is

- Web application that allows price comparison across various online stores by consuming an API
- Facilitates comparison of different footwear retailers, empowering users to make informed economic decisions and potentially save 10% 20% on their purchases

### Languages

Spanish Nativo English 82

#### Skills

 Communication • Teamwork Troubleshooting · Object Oriented Programming (OOP) API REST MVC HTML5 Css JavaScript TypeScript React.js Express.js Node.js Java · Spring Boot • Microsoft SQL Server • PostgreSQL MongoDB MySQL Git • Github Jest Docker